Woodrow Wilson Collection, 1837-1986 (bulk 1883-1924 ): Preliminary Finding Aid MC168
Public Policy Papers
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1810-1992; 17 Volumes; 34 boxes
  - General A-Z, 1810-1963; 7 boxes
    - 2 TLsS, Capps, Wilton R, 1910; 1923; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - TLS, Chambers, W. L, 1913; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - TLS, Children of the District of Columbia, 1922; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - 2 ALS, to Claghorn*-Claghorn, Eugene, 1929; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder F.12)
    - 4 TLsS regarding Woodrow Wilson's cabinet, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - ALS by Baker, Newton D., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - ALS by Garrison, Lindley M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - TLS by Daniels, Josephus, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - TLS by Wilson, W. B., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - TLS by Alexander, Joshua W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - TLS by Redfield, William C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - ALS, Clark, Edward P, 1899; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - 2 TLsS, Clark, John Bates, 1907-1908; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - 1 ALS (Photostat), 1887; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - TLS, Clarke, Dumont, Junior, 1907; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - TLS, Clemons, W. H, 1908; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - TLS, Clemons, W. H, 1909; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - TLS, Clemons, W. H, 1911; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - TLS, Clemons, W. H, 1911; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - TLS, Clemons, W. H, 1911; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - TLS, Clemons, W. H, 1911; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - TLS, Clemons, W. H, 1912; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - TLS, Clemons, W. H, 1912; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - 20 TLsS, Cobb, Frank I, 1914-1923; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - ALS (with transcript), Cobb, Frank I., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - 3 TLsS, Cobb, Frank I, 1922; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Printed announcement of wedding of Wilson, Woodrow and Bolling Galt, Edith, Cogswell, Miss, 1915; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - ALS, Collins, Mr. Varnum Lansing, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - 2 TLsS, Collins, Mr. Varnum Lansing, 1903; 1904; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - 2 TLsS, Collins, Mr. (Varnum Lansing), 1912-1914; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - 9 TLsS, Colver, William B, 1916-1922; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - 1 TL (copy) by Colver to Wilson, Woodrow, 1920; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - 1 condolence card (acknowledgement) by Wilson, Edith Bolling, to Colver, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - 1 TLS, 1921; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - 1 TL (copy), unsigned, 1916; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - TLS, Comstock, Antoinette C, 1907; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - TLS, Cook, Pierre F, 1910; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - ALS, Corwin, Allen W, 1900; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - TLS, Cowl, Jane, 1917; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Telegram, Cox, James, 1917; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - TLS (stamped), Crew, Henry, 1906; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - TLS (with Photostat), Cunningham, J. A, 1911; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - TLS, Currie, Mungo J, 1902; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - TL (carbon), Dabney, R. Heath (copy) of letter to Dabney which was published in The Richmond Times, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - TLS, David, Elizabeth H, 1914; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - LS, David, Dr, 1910; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - TL (draft), Davis, E. P, 1913; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - TLS, Davis, John T, 1910; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - TLS, Day, Fank Miles, 1909; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - TLS, Dearborn, A, 1903; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - TLS, De Rider, J. H, 1904; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - TLS, Dewey, John, 1918; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - TLS, The DIAL, 1910; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - 2 TLsS, Dinsmore, Thomas M, 1911; 1912; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - 43 TLsS, Dodge, Cleveland H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - 3 ALsS, 1902-1911; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - 1 ALS to Dodge, Mrs, 1902; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - 1 ALS to Dodge, William E, 1903; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - 1 AL to Dodge, William E, 1903; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - 1 TLS (copy) to "My dear Momo,", 1909; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - 1 TL (copy with Xerox) by Dodge, Bayard to Boyd, Julian, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - 3 ALsS, Dodge, Cleveland H, 1912; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - 1 ACS, 1911; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - 39 TLsS, 1912-16, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - 1 telegram, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - 1 printed invitation, 1913; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - 1 printed address, inscribed, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - 1 ALS by Axson Wilson, Ellen, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - 1 ALS by Dodge to Wilson, Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - 32 TLsS, Dodge, Cleveland H, 1917-1923; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - 2 telegrams to Dodge, Mr. and Mrs. Cleveland H, 1921; 1923; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - 8 ALsS by Wilson, Edith Bolling, 1-1920 7-undated, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - 5 TLsS, 1924-1925; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - 1 AL (draft) by Dodge to Wilson, Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - 1 TL (carbon) by Dodge to Wilson, Woodrow, 1920; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - 2 TLsS by Baker, Ray Stannard to Dodge, Mrs. Cleveland H, 1927; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - TLS, Dolon, Park E, 1923; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - TLS, Drinkwater, John, 1921; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder F.2)
    - 2 TLsS (stamped signature), Duffiel, H. G, 1906; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - TLS, Duffield, H. G, 1906; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - TLS, Duffield, H. G., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Printed announcement, Duffield, Mrs, 1915; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - TLS, Duncan, W. Butler, 1903; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - TLS, Duneka, A, 1911; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - TLS, Dutch, Herbert W, 1909; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - TLS, EAGLE (Brooklyn Eagle?), 1902; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - TLS, Edelman, Louis, 1909; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - TLS, Edmons, Richard H, 1912; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - TLS, Ely, Robert Erskine, 1907; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - TLS, Erdman, Walter C, 1912; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - ALS, Evelyn College for Women regarding Howe Jr., George, 1895; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Aerogram, Fasig, L. O. (Mrs.), 1912; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - 7 TLsS, Felt, Zephaniah Charles, 1904-1916; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - 1 TMs (draft), c., 1904; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - 1 printed article THE LAMP, 1902; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - TLS, Fentress, David, 1899; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - TLS, Fentress, David, 1902; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - LS, Fentress, David (Mrs.), 1907; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - TLS, Ferguson, Charles, 1913; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - TLS, Ferguson, Charles, 1915; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - ALS, Fielder, J. W. Jr, 1895; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - TLS, Fielder, J. W. Jr, 1902; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - TLS, Fielder, John W, 1902; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - TLS, Fillebrown, D. B, 1902; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - TL (copy), Fine, Henry B, 1913; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - 3 TLsS, Fine, May Margaret, 1909-1918; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - TLS, Fiske, Haley, 1922; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - TLS, Fiske, Haley, 1923; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - TLS, Ford, Henry Jones, 1916; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - TLS, Day, Frank Miles and brother, 1908; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - 3 TLsS, Day, Frank Miles and brother, 1909; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - TLS (letter of recommendation), about Frederick, K. T, 1903; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - TLS, Frothingham, Arthur L, 1905; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Print announcement, Garmany, Francis C. (Mr. and Mrs.), 1915; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - TLS, 1915; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - 1 place card, Garmany, Frank C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - 24 TLsS, Garrett, Robert, 1904-1916; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - 3 TLsS to Garrett by Tumulty, J.P., 1913-1916; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - TLS, 1904; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - TLS, 1907; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - 11 TLsS, 1907-1911; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - 1 TL (copy) to "My dear Momo,", 1909; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - 1 TL (copy) by Porter, William Cooper to West, Andrew F, 1909; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - 1 document (resolution regarding the Graduate School), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - TLS, Gerould, James Thayer, 1923; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - TLS (with transcript), Gilder, Richard Watson, 1897; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - ALS, 1898; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - TLS, Goodhue, E. S, 1912; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - TLS, Gordon, George A, 1910; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - TLS, Gordon, J. Maxwell, 1911; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - TLS, Gould, E. R. L, 1898; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - TLS, Griffith, William, 1912; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - TLS, Hale, Matthew, 1917; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - 2 TLsS (rubberstamp), Hale, William Bayard, 1912; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - 1 TLS by Tumulty, Joseph P., to Hale, 1916; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - TLS, Hamilton, S. M. (Mrs.), 1914; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - 2 clippings, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - 7 TLsS, Hapgood, Norman, 1912-1920; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - 2 TLsS, Harding, John R, 1910-1912; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - TLS by Tumulty, J.P., to Harding, 1918; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - LS, Harkins, William F, 1910; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - 1 ALS, Harper, George M, 1903; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - 2 TLsS, 1913; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - 2 calling cards, one an ANS (initialed), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - 2 calling cards of Mrs. Wilson, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - 2 TLsS, Harper and Brothers, 1900; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - 1 AL (draft) with typed copy signed by Alden, Henry M, 1900; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - 1 TLS to Harper, J. Henry, 1899; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - 3 TLsS to Alden, Henry M, 1900; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - 1 telegram to Alden, Henry M, 1895; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - 1 document, draft of contact, 1900; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - 1 AL (draft) with typed copy signed by Alden, Henry M, 1895; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - 2 TLsS, Harris, Anna, 1910; 1914; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - TLS, Hart, Albert Bushnell, 1902; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - 2 TLsS, Harvier, Ernest, 1912; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - TLS, Haughton, Perry O, circa 1810-1910; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - TLS, Hazelton, John H, 1905; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - 3 ALsS, Henderson, Robert R, 1897-1901; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - 14 TLsS, 1899-1921; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - 1 TL, 1915; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - 1 telegram, 1915; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - 1 LS, 1909; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - 1 TLsS by Wilder, William R, to Henderson, 1902; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - TL (copy) by Wilson, Woodrow to Bridges, Robert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - TLS to Henneman, John Bell, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64A)
    - ACS to Henneman, John Bell, 1894 October 10; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64A)
    - ACS to Henneman, John Bell, 1897 August 26; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64a)
    - TCS to J. B. H., 1904 February 10; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 64a)
    - TLS, Henry, Thomas M, 1909; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - TLS (Xerox) by Henry to Wilson, Woodrow, 1909; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - TLS, 1910; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - 1 ALS (not in Wilson's hand and signed with a rubber stamp), Hewett, W. T, 1896; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - 2 TLsS, 1902; 1911; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - 2 TLsS, Hibben, John Grier, 1917; 1918; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ALS, Hillard, Miss, 1900; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ALS, Hillegass, O. J, 1910; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - TLS, Hirschfield, Benjamin L, 1912; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 3 TLsS, Hiscox, E. T, 1910-1916; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 4 TLsS, Hitchcock, Gilbert M, 1914; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - ALS, Hoagland, Jesse M. (About), 1910; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - TLS, Hollis, Henry F, 1913; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - TLS, Hollis, Henry F, 1918; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 2 TLsS, Holt, Hamilton, 1918; 1920; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - TL by House, House, E. M. to Wilson, Woodrow, 1912; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - TLS (with photostat), Hovey, Harriet C, 1902; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 5 AlsS, Howe, Edward L, 1904; 1910; 1913; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 11 TLsS, 1908; 1916; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - TL (draft), Hughes, Senator, 1913; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - TLS, Hulbert, Allen S, 1913; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - ALS, Hutton, Laurence, 1901; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - ALS, Hutton, Laurence, 1901; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - ALS, Hutton, Laurence, 1902; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - ALS, Hutton, Laurence (Mrs.), 1902; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - ALS, Isham, William B, 1895; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - TLS, Isham, William B, 1910; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - TLS, Isham, William B, 1914; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - TLS, Jessup, Everet C, 1912; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - ALS, Johnson, Charles W. L, 1903; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - TLS, Johnson, H. S, 1907; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - 3 TLsS, Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1902; 1911; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - TLS, Joline, Adrian H, 1904; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - ALS, Joline, Mr. (Adrian H. Joline), 1900; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - TLS, Kelley, William V, 1903; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - TLS, Kemmerer, E. W, 1913; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Shorthand draft of letter with transcription, Kendall, Calvin N., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - 6 TLs, Kerry, John T., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - 1 ALS by Kerr to his family, 1915; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - 1 printed wedding announcement, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - 2 place cards, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - TLS, Klauder, Charles Z, 1920; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - TLS, Kleiser, Grenville, 1910; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - ALS, Knight, James C, 1894; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - TLS, Kraft, William J, 1911; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - TLS, Landon, Francis G., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - TL (copy) by Landon to Wilson, Woodrow, 1918; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - TLS (with photocopy), Lansing, Robt. (Secretary of State), 1916; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - TLS, Lantz, C, 1910; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - TLS, Lawson, Victor, 1912; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - ALS, Ledwith, W. L, 1902; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - ALS, Lee, Francis, 1891; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - TLS, Levey, Frederick H, 1910; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - TLS, Lippmann, Walter, 1917; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - 6 TLsS, Lynch, B. (Frederick), 1912-1915; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - 2 TLsS, Macfarland, Charles S, 1913; 1914; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - 2 TLsS, MacKay, David L., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - 1 ALS by Mackay to Wilson, Woodrow, clipping, 1910; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - TLS, MacKenzie, James C, 1893; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - ALS, MacKenzie, James C, 1893; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - TLS, MacLaren, W. S, 1912; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - TLS, MacMurray, John V. A, 1913; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - 2 TLsS, Magie, W. F., 1909-10, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - TLS, Maone, Dudley Field, 1916; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - TLS, Marine, Richard E, 1917; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - ALS, Marquand, Allan, 1902; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - 2 TLsS, Marshall, Thomas R, 1916-1917; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - 1 TL (copy), message of congratulations by Marshall to Wilson, Woodrow, 1916; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - 2 telegrams, Marshall, Thomas R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - ACS, McAdoo, William Gibbs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 5 TLsS, McAlpin, Charles W, 1912-1914; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 1 TLS to Maone, Dudley Field, 1914; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 12 TLsS, McAlpin, Charles W, 1915-1917; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - 12 TLsS, McAlpin, Charles W, 1918-1922; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Printed invitation, McAlpin, Charles W. (Mr. and Mrs.), 1913; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 2 TLsS, McClellan, William, 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - TLS, McClure, H. S, 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - TLS, McClure, H. S, 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - TLS, McClure, H. S, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 1 TLS, McClure, H. S, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - 1 ALS by McClure to secretary Princeton University, 1929; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - ALS regarding Thomas, Harvey; McCombs, William F, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 1 photocopy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - TLS, McCormick, S. D, 1894; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - LS, McCormick, S. D, 1894; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - TLS, McCullagh, Archibald, 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - TLS, McGowan, Patrick F, 1911; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - 2 TLsS, McIlwain, Charles H, 1905; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - 1 ALS, 1906; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - 2 TLsS, McIlwaine, Richards, 1893; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - TLS, McKay, W, 1892; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - 1 photograph of McKay, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - 2 TLsS, McLure, Norman R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - 1 TLS by McLure to Thompson, Lawrance, 1938; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - 2 TLsS (photostats), 1903; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - 1 TLS by McLure to Thompson, Lawrance, 1938; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - TLS by Tumulty, Joseph P.; McNally, E. P, 1921; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - TLS, McPherson, Simon J, 1908; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 22A)
    - 2 TLsS, Merrill, William Daxton, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 22B)
    - TLS, Milbank, Albert G, 1918; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - TLS, Miller, Charles S, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - 1 telegram, Moors, John F, 1922; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - 1 telegram (copy) by Moors to Wilson, Woodrow, and others, 1921; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - TL (2 copies) by Baker, Newton D., to Wilson, Woodrow, 1923; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - TLS, Morehouse, Edward W, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - List of electoral votes in 1912 election, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - 1 ALS (xerox copy), Morgan, Junius (Mrs.), 1908; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - 1 ALS (xerox copy), 1908; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - TLS 1904 Morris, Benjamin Wistar, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - TLS by Morris to Wilson, 1904; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - 21 TLsS, 1904-1906; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - 1 photostat, 1905; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - 1 TLS to Payne, W. A, 1906; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - 4 TLsS (initialed) by Morris to Wilson, Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - 1 TL (copy) by Borglum, Gutzon, to Wilson, Woodrow, with ANS to Morris added, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - 2 TLsS (initialed) by Morris to Guerin, Jules, 1904-1905; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - 1 ALS by Guerin to Morris, 1905; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - LS by Guerin to Morris, 1904; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - 1 TL (initialed) by Morris, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - ALS, Morris, Benjamin Wistar, 1905; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - 7 TLsS, Morris, Benjamin Wistar, 1906-1907; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - 3 TLsS, Mountsier, Robert, 1908; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - 1 TLS by Close, Gilbert F, 1908; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - TLS, Munroe, James P, 1903; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - TLS, Munroe, James P, 1918; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - TLS, Murphree, A. A, 1913; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - TLS, Nash, Theo (about), (letter of recommendation), 1913; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - TLS, Nixono, Horace T, 1911; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - TLS, Nugent, Edward, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - TLS, Osborn, Arthur H, 1907; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - TLS, Osborn, Hannah F, 1902; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - TLS, Osborn, Henry F, 1909; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - 2 TLsS by Stearns, Alfred E, 1906; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - ALS by Page to Wilson, Woodrow; Page, Walter H, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - TLS, Pavey, Darwin C, 1918; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - 2 ALsS, Peck, M. A. (Mrs.), 1909; 1911; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - 1 telegram, Peck, M. A. (Mrs.), 1911; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - TLS, Peck, Vincent, 1898; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Printed invitations, Peters, J. E. (Rev. and Mrs.), 1903; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - 3 TLsS, Pfeiffer, T. Newell, 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - TLS, Pinci, A. R, 1913; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - TLS, Polk, Charles C, 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - TLS, "The Pope" (regarding Dumont Clarke, Junior), 1907; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - TLS, Presbrey, Frank S, 1915; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - 2 TLsS, Priest, George M, 1915; 1917; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - TLS, Priest, George M, 1921; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - TL (copy), Priest, George M, 1921; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - TL (copy), Priest, George M., to Geroud, James T., (copy), 1925; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - 2 TLS (copies) to Wilson, Woodrow, 1921; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - AL (draft), Princeton University, undated; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - TL (carbon), Board of Trustees, undated; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - TLS, Purcell, A. M, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - TLS, Rawnsley, H. D, 1919; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - TLS, Reichner, L. Irving, 1914; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 18 ALsS, Reid, Harry (Mrs.), 1897-1902; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 4 ALsS, Reid, Harry (Mrs.), 1903; 1907; 1910; 1912; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 16 TLsS, Reid, Harry (Mrs.), 1912; 1921; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 1 TL, Reid, Harry (Mrs.), 1913; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 1 ANS, Reid, Harry (Mrs.), 1923; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - TLS, Rice, Melvin A, 1914; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - ALS, Richardson, O. W, 1908; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - TLS, Richardson, O. W, 1906; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - TLS, Roe, Charles T, 1911; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 4 TLsS, Rogers, Walter S, 1917-1920; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 9)